[Music]
[Música]
What happened to Andrea now that she had
Qué le ha pasado a Andrea ahora que ha
a problem with Win michu, let's see, I
tenido una movida con Win michu a ver yo
saw a tweet from Pablo saying that
he visto un twet de Pablo diciendo que
Win michu wants to sue him,
Win michu lo quiere demandar se anuncia
a lawsuit is being announced by wismichu against
una demanda de parte de wismichu contra
andresita F Ah, they have
andresita F Ah contra Andrea han
sued Andrea Andrea dalis veira a photo
demandado a Andrea dalis veira una foto
of wismichu and this miniature that it seems she
de wismichu y esta miniatura que se ve
loved I believe michu after
que le ha encantado Yo cre michu después
the last procedures that she
de los últimos procedimientos que que
ordered one that was Nauter and another
encargó uno que fue el de nauter y otro
that was Well there is another one that there are some
que fue Bueno hay otro que no hay
procedures that
algunos procedimientos que no han
these people haven't told yet eh Javi I
contado esta gente todavía eh Javi yo te
motivate you and I'll train you feiler But you live
motivo y te entreno feiler Pero tú vives
here in Seville because I'm seeing that you
aquí en Sevilla porque estoy viendo que
give me dollars but if you want to
me das Dólares pero si me quieres
motivate me, let's see suggestions I mean no no no
motivar a ver sugerencias O sea no no no
I haven't seen him as much more motivated to
lo he visto yo como mucho más motivado a
sue Wi michu seeing how
demandar a Wi michu viendo cómo le
the lawsuits he filed turned out, no he
salieron los los pleitos que puso no que
said he was going to sue 8000
decía que iba a demandar a 8000
youtubers and he didn't sue any of them,
youtubers y no demandó a ninguno tío
this guy eh In case you're new and
este eh Por si venís nuevos y
such, the issue is very simple, a youtuber  he
tal el tema es muy sencillo un youtuber
does char roulet where he asks
coge hace char rulet donde le pide a las
girls to show him their tits and then what he
niñas que le enseñen las tetas y él lo
does is take that content and
que hace luego es [__] ese contenido y
upload it to his website eh uncensored and
subirlo a su página web eh sin censura y
for you to see lauti a kiss a kiss a
para tu ver lauti un beso un beso un
kiss lauti a huge kiss I mean he
beso lauti un besote enorme o sea se ha
got into the subject char roulet well
metido en el tema char rulet bueno tema
delicate subject that is a very delicate subject the
delicado eso es un tema muy delicado la
truth eh I even let's see if the subject is about that the
verdad eh yo incluso a ver si el tema
same I even skip
trata de eso lo mismo incluso me salto
the extract eh it is a subject that I that I it
el extracto eh es un tema que yo me que
is a subject that I go out dust a
yo es un tema que yo me sal polvor un
kiss when he and Dala were
beso cuando él y dala se estaban
fighting I skipped that subject even I
peleando Yo ese tema me lo salté incluso
mean because I see it as a delicate subject it is
o sea porque lo ve un tema delicado es
an ugly subject you know No not because I don't have my
un tema feo sabes No no por no tenga mi
opinion eh that I do I have my
opinión eh que la tengo yo tengo mis
folders I have my things you know
carpetas yo tengo mis cosas sabes
M it is a subject that I don't I don't like the
M es un tema que no me no me agrada la
truth I don't like them he tells me place I have
verdad no me simpatizan me dice lugar he
omitted Well in the end these are things that they
omitido Bueno al final son cosas que
are saying among themselves they
están diciendo entre ellos ellos se las
manage man and they need your course
apañar mán y ellos necesitamos tu curso
on how to papebes at 80 years old and
de como papear probes a los 80 años y
with 50 children and  seeing you under 30 and
con 50 hijos y verte con menos de 30 y
having that great hair with all due respect okay
tener ese pelazo con todo respeto vale
seen the issues we have to react to the
visto los temas hay que reaccionar al
Spartac Dallas video and check out the
video de espartac Dallas y revisar la
wu community you are lukewarm Javier no I
comunidad wu sos un tibio Javier no no
am not lukewarm it's that let's see on the one hand It's
soy un tibio es que a ver por una parte
that Win michu is like apart that's what I
Es que Win michu está como apartado eso
think when people are like
eso creo que cuando la gente está como
apart in Yes I think look if I
apartada en Sí yo creo que mira si yo
went back Maybe I would answer him
volviera atrás A lo mejor le contestaba
and tell him a few things that
y le decía unas cuantas de cositas que a
maybe he doesn't know trust you my
lo mejor no sabe fíate tú me vino el
friend came to me to start a conversation with the
colega a sacar una conversación con los
audios that are out there with the videos
audios que hay por ahí con los vídeos
that are out there and I'm not referring to this
que hay por ahí y no me refiero a esto
eh I mean I haven't even gotten into this I mean
eh o sea ni me he metido en esto O sea
when he was fighting with Dallas I didn't
cuando él se estaba peleando con Dallas
even get into this this topic I
ni me metí en esto este tema yo me lo
skipped it directly people and I also didn't
salté directamente gente e tampoco me
get too involved in the issue of the audios that
metí mucho en lo del tema de los audios
Ingrid was talking to people and
eso que Ingrid fue hablando con gente y
Ingrid was putting it green to the other
Ingrid fue poniéndolo verde a a la otra
eh And when what happened to me when what
eh Y cuando me pasó lo de la cuando me
happened to me with the conversations You know what
pasó lo de las conversaciones Sabes cuál
the problem was man my
fue el problema hombre que mi
thought was to report my thought It's to
pensamiento era denunciar mi pensamiento
report but my  lawyer there
Es denunciar pero mi abogado ahí Eso no
Pablo doesn't handle that, the issues with these
lo lleva Pablo eso los temas con esta
people are handled by another lawyer who is the one who
gente los lleva otro abogado que es el
has won now the issue of something is worth
que ha ganado ahora el tema de algo vale
Why, simply because he knows the
Por qué pues simplemente porque conoce a
protagonists no Hi Javi
los a los protagonistas no Hola Javi
I arrived tender and loosening kiss ciru
lleg yo tiernito y aflojando beso ciru
how are you sweetheart And then basically
qué tal corazón Y entonces básicamente
Well, when you are going to take action
Pues cuando tú vas a emprender acciones
and you are going to open a lawsuit against someone,
y vas a abrir un pleito contra alguien
well, it is better to respond to justice and
pues pues mejor responder la justicia y
not in parallel on the internet no but
no paralelamente en internet no pero tal
maybe I should have responded
vez sí que tuve que haber respondido
because in the end I don't know if we are
porque al final no sé si esa denuncia la
going to file that complaint I don't know if we are going to go
vamos a poner no sé si vamos a tirar por
elsewhere with other things it is that I get
otro lado con otras cosas es que me da
really lazy sometimes in the
un montón de pereza algunas veces en el
extract my you okay
extracto mi ti vale
eh For me to take legal action it has to
eh Para yo tomar medidas legales tiene
be something that affects me so much so much so much
que ser una cosa que me toque tantísimo
or I know or someone who does
tantísimo tantísimo o se o alguien que
n't stop otherwise you know why
no pare de otra manera sabes por qué
because Javi answer him and bury
pues porque Javi respóndele y entierra
the wismi eh Lone I don't think you can
al wismi eh Lone No creo que se pueda
bury a person who is already buried I
enterrar una persona que ya está
mean what are you going to say about being
enterrada O sea qué vas a decir lo de
cool debating about whether they are minors or
chulé debatir sobre si son menores o son
adults or I don't know what what am I going to  debate
mayores o no sé qué qué voy a debatir
that is an issue of him with Dallas Dallas
eso es un tema de él con Dallas Dallas
exposed it Dallas Dallas exposed his side
lo expuso Dallas Dallas expuso su parte
Win michu exposed his arguments too
Win michu expuso sus argumentos también
let's debate now come on if you pay
vamos a a debatir ahora vamos es que si
attention to those people little more and that he did
le haces caso a esa gente poco más y que
n't even become famous for the chulé
ni siquiera se hizo famoso por los chulé
you understand what I'm saying I mean I didn't
me entiendes qué te digo o sea ni
even give my opinion on the filing of the
siquiera opiné del archivo del
procedure you know I have my opinion
procedimiento sabes que tengo mi opinión
But it is a very delicate subject I prefer not to
Pero es un tema muy delicado prefiero no
get into that and I would have the right to have done so
meterme en eso y tendría derecho para
after his moment but
haberlo hecho después de su momento pero
well if at some point again eh
bueno si en algún momento otra vez eh se
the canyon opens Well maybe I'll decide to
abre el cañón Pues a lo mejor ya decido
comment on a few things that I didn't
comentar unas cuantas de cosas que no
comment on in his day not a few
comenté en su día no unos cuantos de
topics that I skipped okay but what are we
temas que me salté vale pero es que qué
going to refute So
vamos a rebatir O sea que denuncie
wismichu denounced Dallas he hasn't sued him he
wismichu a Dallas no lo ha demandado no
hasn't denounced him for that however there are
lo ha denunciado por eso sin embargo hay
other procedures out there of
otros procedimientos por ahí de chorras
[ __ ] [ __ ] and yet he hasn't
de chorradas y sin embargo no ha
sued Win michu he hasn't sued
demandado a Win michu no ha demandado a
Dallas with all those videos that he
Dallas con con todos los vídeos esos que
made they only talked also in the
hizo solo hablaron también en la
discussion recently he sued nauter
tertulia hace poco demandó a nauter
because he called him a jerk I don't know what I don't know
porque le dijo cabronazo No sé qué no sé
how many little words you know Eh You're very
cuántas palabritas sabes Eh Vas muy
chill well Andrés until not Go chill
chill bueno Andrés hasta que no Vaya
until not go chill each one
chill hasta que no vaya chill cada uno
who knows how to choose their moment mm He
que sepa elegir su momento mm demandó
also sued another kid another youtuber
también a otro chaval a otro youtuber
too but that lawsuit is that I never
también pero esa demanda es que nunca
knew the content the truth But I
supe el contenido la verdad Pero me
imagine it would be the same insults and
imagino que sería lo mismo insultos y
bad language and so on you know but it's like
mala lengua y demás sabes pero es como
this topic Why don't you know and now he's
este tema Por qué no sabes y ahora está
saying that he's going to sue Andrea and
diciendo que va a demandar Andrea y a
Pablo no because I saw a tweet about Pablo
Pablo no porque vi un tweet sobre Pablo
about how he wanted to sue Pablo well let him
sobre que quería demandar a Pablo bueno
sue him Pablo I don't see it I haven't
que lo demande Pablo no lo veo yo no lo
seen him scared of Pablo and nothing dude
he visto con miedo a Pablo y nada tío
now the bad guy It's me for telling it I
que ahora la mala Soy yo por contarlo o
mean m I think it's phenomenal the truth I mean
sea m me parece fenomenal la verdad O
I'm perfectly set up to be the bad guy
sea yo perfecta puesta para ser la mala
I swear So nothing I'm waiting I
te lo juro Así que nada estoy esperando
'm waiting I mean no I'm not
estoy esperando o sea no no les tengo
scared of them I mean eh lukewarm shur one of my
miedo o sea eh tibio shur uno de mis
followers Look at me for having but I do
seguidores Mira yo por tener pero es que
n't want to get into that Really I
no me quiero meter en eso De verdad O
mean I mean for having I even have an article
sea yo por tener tengo hasta un artículo
that his own lawyer retweeted and I have it
que retuiteó su propio abogado y lo
saved and certified that how are you
tengo guardado y certificado que como
going to who are you going to  sue because he
vas a quién vas a demandar porque él
said that well in the Nauter trial
decía que bueno en el juicio de nauter
apparently he said that he was going to sue
por lo visto dijo que iba a demandar a
Tokichi of course I was thinking who are you going to
tokichi claro yo pensaba quién vas a
sue if you have your own
demandar si es que tienes a a tu propio
lawyer challenging this you know You know what you
abogado retando esto sabes Sabes qu es
should have a closed closet yeah
lo que deberías tener ropero cerrado sí
Okay but okay let's see come on let me find out he showed
Bueno pero bueno a ver venga que yo me
me a clip saying eh here
entere me sacó un clip diciendo eh aquí
is part two of the video against Win
está la parte dos del vídeo contra Win
michu Andresita eh substitute for l loves
michu andresita eh sustituta de l amores
tells me Luare what's up 10 Yeah well
me dice luare que pasa el 10 Sí bueno
More or less they are the songs of Cha Roulet
Más o menos son los temas de Cha roulet
okay I can imagine but the thing is that I
vale que me imagino pero es que yo me
imagine that Win michu hasn't even
imagino que Win michu ni siquiera habrá
said anything no or or Who said that
dicho nada no o o Quién ha dicho que
Who said that there is a lawsuit that
Quién ha dicho que hay una demanda que
could come to be but it is totally
puede llegar a ser pero es totalmente
understandable totally understandable and understandable he is
comprensible totalmente comprensible y
too handsome and
entendible es demasiado guapo y
too smart I am not going to tell you that
demasiado listo no te voy a decir yo que
no other bad thing about him so I can't
no otra cosa mala de él así es que no se
think of absolutely anything because I don't
me ocurre absolutamente nada porque no
know him personally the only thing I
lo conozco personalmente lo único que
know is his public figure and from there
conozco es su figura pública y de ahí No
Nothing bothers me no Nauter won Don't [ __ ] with me Do
me molesta nada no nauter le ganó No
n't [ __ ] with me And what did he lose
jodas No jodas Y qué fue lo que perdió
then that  there the lawsuit deuter
entonces que de ahí la demanda deuter
estimated cu word such and he had to pay
estimaron cu palabr tal Y tuvo que pagar
na I think it was 1000 or rather the colleague
na creo que fueron 1000 o sea el colega
spent but I have already explained that
se gastó pero eso ya ya lo he explicado
a million times the colleague spent the
un millón de veces el colega se gastó el
money that his lawyer costs which
dinero que cuesta el abogado suyo que
costs a fortune in suing
cuesta un dineral en en demandar a
nauter and the intention he had in
nauter y la intención que tenía
suing nauter I have already explained
demandando a nauter ya lo expliqué
when you see these people doing these
cuando veáis esta gente haciendo los
legal procedures that they open and
procedimientos legales estos que abren y
so on always look for a translation for
demás siempre buscarle una traducción a
his story okay When I say his story
su relato vale Cuando digo a su relato
is what they want to change from the
es lo que ellos quieren cambiar de la
story to sell from the story and from the
historia vender de la historia y de la
I sincerely It is that I believe that those are
yo sinceramente Es que creo que eso son
all ideas of the lady you give
ideas todas de la de la señora das
permission to touch me inappropriately
permiso para tocarme inapropiadamente
listening to you please man please and
escuchándote por favor tío por favor e
I sincerely believe that they are ideas of the
yo sinceramente creo que son ideas de la
lady and they follow her and that's it and
señora y ellos le siguen y ya está y la
the nauter lawsuit was and the lawsuit against
la demanda nauter era e la demanda a
nauter was eh with the issue of Andorra
nauter era eh con el tema de de andorra
and the criminal record Also he himself in
y de los antecedentes Además él mismo en
his live broadcasts said I have sued people
sus directos decía he demandado a gente
since he told me that I have had a criminal
ya que me ha dicho que yo he tenido
record and then you went to the
antecedentes y luego te fuiste a la
lawsuit and the lawsuit was for insults you
demanda y la demanda era por insulto
know  and spend I don't know how much
sabes y gastarte no sé cuánto
risk losing the cars you know
arriesgarte a perder las cochas sabes
risk losing the cars dude I
arriesgarte a perder las cochas tío O
mean little more and you pay and Palmas the
sea que poco más y pagas y Palmas las
costs no I don't know the truth I don't understand
costas no no sé la verdad no entiendo
these moves let's say yes I understand them
las movidas estas vamos si las entiendo
and I know where they go we know his his name
y sé por dónde van sabemos su su nombre
Marcos Gregorio lost something
Marcos Gregorio perdió algo contra
against this guy but I don't know exactly
contra este tío pero no sé exactamente
what I think and And that it pisses me off it
el Qué creo y Y eso que me toque los
pisses me off nauter
huevos que me toque los huevos nauter
won in the sense that or rather the same
ganó en el sentido de que o sea igual
as this is what dal veira is saying I
que esto lo está diciendo dal veira O
mean no Win michu hasn't said anything
sea no Win michu no ha dicho nada lo
dalira is saying it but of course if she
está diciendo dalira pero claro si lo
is saying it the accounts could
está diciendo las cuentas esas pueden
also come the information there or have they
venir también la información por ahí o
told you put it no this is fay the one who
les han dicho tú ponlo no esto es fay la
can confirm it wasn't fay in
que lo puede confirmar no estaba fay en
the chat that he didn't have to pay almost anything
el chat que no tuvo que pagar casi nada
of what was asked of him well over there eh
de lo que le pedía po bien por ahí eh
but they only sentenced him to 1.5 € because
pero solo le condenaron a 1,5 € porque
the judge said that they both had the same
el juez dijo que los dos eran igual de
mouth flip-flops let's see I don't know if I'm
boca chanclas a ver yo no sé si estoy
saying something too much too much mm like that
diciendo algo demasiado demasiado mm así
but [ __ ] the only thing I'm saying is
pero [__] lo único que estoy diciendo es
that there is public evidence of everything and that they
que hay pruebas públicas de todo y que
don't touch me  the noses or rather That's it, that's it,
no me toquen las narices o sea Ya está
at no time am I
ya está en ningún momento le estoy
defaming him or anything like that, I consider I
difamando ni nada de eso considero te
want to tell you
quiero decir
eh I'm simply saying everything
eh estoy diciendo simplemente todo lo
that I've seen, everything that's collected
que he visto todo lo que está recogido
on the internet, everything that everyone
en internet todo lo que todo el mundo
knows, the crazy bottles they told him is
sabe el el botellas loca le decían es
obv uter will win if the other day Bot already
obv uter ganara si el otro día Bot ya
but it has nothing to do with leaving the
pero no tiene nada que ver lo de dej el
issue of the bottles aside it's another
tema de las botellas de lado es otro
issue please And that man that I know
tema por favor Y eso tío que yo que sé
I'm afraid What what if obviously
yo miedo A qué a qué si obviamente está
everything is collected in a public way there are
todo recogido de forma pública hay
testimonies of girls and such and and there are
testimonios de de chicas y tal y y hay
a lot of old tweets and such of which there
un montón de tweets antiguos y tal de
are screenshots How many
los que de los que hay capturas Cuántos
years since How many years has it been since
años de que Cuántos años hace de que
Dallas made those videos to Win michu
Dallas le hizo esos vídeos a Win michu
Okay guys within 3 days or rather, due to
Bueno chicos dentro de 3 días o sea por
criminal law this no longer happened or rather at
lo penal esto ya no no fue o sea por lo
least as far as we know, I think we
menos hasta donde sabemos creo que nos
would have found out Okay as far as we
hubiésemos enterado Vale hasta donde
know, criminal law expires in a year Javi
sabemos em penal prescriba al año Javi
Why can you see a red baby doll in your closet
Por qué en tu ropero se ve un baby doll
Close the door Grandpa a kiss a
rojo Cierra la puerta Abuelo un beso un
kiss eh what the hell is a baby doll What is
beso eh qué [__] es un baby doll Qué es
that eh  within 13 days it would already have
eso eh dentro de 13 días ya estaría
expired This particular video is worth the
prescrito Este vídeo en concreto vale
others are older what the [ __ ] is
los los otros son anteriores qué [__] es
a baby doll sucking my ass look at you [ __ ] off I mean
un baby doll chuparme el miros al [__]
videos of Dallas saying these
o sea vídeos de Dallas diciéndole estas
things Look at Dallas is live By
cosas Mira Dallas está en directo Por
the way videos of Dallas saying these
cierto vídeos de Dallas diciéndole estas
things
cosas
eh eh Finally I don't know if this this one is from
eh eh Por fin no sé si este este es del
February 11th meaning this in 6
11 de febrero o sea este dentro de 6
days this video is expired
días está prescrito este vídeo o sea
it means that yes yes yes yes
prescrito quiere decir que si si si si
wismichu hasn't filed a lawsuit it already
no ha puesto wismichu una demanda ya
means that a baby doll is not going to file it
significa que no la va a poner un baby
what the [ __ ] is But how am I going to know
doll qué [__] es Pero cómo voy a saber
what is clear whoever uses it will know
lo que es claro lo sabrá el que lo use
what What is that what are you talking about
qué Qué es eso de qué estáis hablando
anyway where am I going with this am I going to
total a dónde voy con esto yo voy a
make accusations or something like that no Of
hacer acusaciones o algo de eso no Por
course not I don't get into that it's that
supuesto que no Yo no me meto en eso es
everyone has spoken out their
que hable la la cada uno ha expuesto su
version everyone has put forward their point they haven't
versión cada uno ha puesto su punto no
taken it to trial they haven't taken
lo han llevado juzgado no lo han llevado
that issue to trial and In that sense there was
a juicio ese tema e En ese sentido hubo
a file I think there was there was a file
un archivo creo que hubo hubo un archivo
that I also didn't comment on not even the
que tampoco comenté ni siquiera la
accusation if I don't if I'm not mistaken eh there
imputación si no me si no me equivoco eh
was a file on the case  and that's what must be
hubo un archivo sobre el caso y es lo
respected and that's it no em
que hay que respetar y y ya está no em
but I'm already telling you So what I'm getting at If
pero que ya os digo O sea a lo que voy
not, if he doesn't sue Dallas, I have my
Si no si no demanda a Dallas tengo yo mi
doubts that he's going to sue someone else for
duda de que vaya a demandar a otro por
the same issue, I mean, and if not And look at you,
ese mismo tema o sea y si no Y fíjate tú
in the title of Dallas now it said
que en el título de Dallas ahora ponía
in the title of Dallas it said MM and you have a
en el título de Dallas ponía MM y tienes
criminal record that's why you can't
antecedentes penales por eso no puedes
go to Andorra and I go [ __ ] yourselves go
ir andorra y yo iros a la [__] iros a
suck it a little what disgusting people man
chuparla un poco qué asco de gente tío
how disgusting you are and also if you don't
qué asco que dais y además si tú no
have anything Why the [ __ ] do you post a
tienes nada Por qué [__] pones un
tweet look at this class why do you
tweet fijaos que esta clase por qué
post an Uy Why do you post a says the following
pones un Uy Por qué pones un dice lo sig
even in public I get bored in
incluso a nivel público me aburro en
class and I check followers they're going to
clase y chequeo seguidoras me van a
take me to jail why do you publish that If you
llevar preso por qué publicas eso Si tú
're not doing anything wrong I want to
no estás haciendo nada malo Te quiero
tell you, you're not afraid, I don't care,
decir no tienes miedo a mí me da igual
man, I mean, it's not that I'm ever going to be
tío o sea yo no es que en la vida le voy
afraid of anyone, I mean, no What's the point of
a tener miedo a nadie o sea no Para qué
being afraid? Hello racher
de qué te sirve tener miedo Hola racher
How are you? How are you? Welcome gorgeous How are you? How are you?
Qué tal Cómo estás bienvenida guapísima
Beautiful queen? And for what? I mean  What good does it do
Qué tal Cómo estás hermosa reina e para
me to be
qué O sea De qué me sirve a mí tenerle
afraid of him, well, like, well, Okay, because of what
miedo pues vale como pues Vale Sí por lo
you say, I mean, you turn off the computer, you turn off
que tú digas o sea vos apagas la sea vos
the computer, you go out with a
apagas la compu te vas a a salí con un
friend or you go out with your girlfriend and the
amigo o salís con tu novia y yo la
truth is, I'm not going to talk to him about, I'm not going with a
verdad no le voy a hablar de no voy con
friend, let's go get something to eat and the first thing I
un amigo vamos a comer algo y lo primero
say to him is what the dog come back I tell him did
que le digo es que perro vuelvea le digo
you see Lucas, Lucas is going to Los
viste que Lucas que Lucas va a a Los
Angeles, I don't know why Gibel is
Ángeles le no sé por qué lo está
saying it, but that happened in 2023,
diciendo gibel Pero eso pasó en el 2023
not in 2023, Quetzal came out talking about
no en el 2023 salió Quetzal hablando de
how Wismichu and Miare would get it on
que wismichu y miare se ponían en la
when they would get together like that, they would get together for dinner,
cuando quedaban así quedaban a cenar los
friends, these groups and so on, they would
amigos los grupos estos y demás se
start talking about Dallas and so,
ponían a hablar de Dallas y y Por ende
for example, one night, of
de por ejemplo en alguna noche de de de
Vín, they would put Vín down, no, no, because
vín la ponían verde a vín no no porque
Vín, I spent them with Dallas, Delox also
vín yo las pasé con Dallas delox también
said that. Well, Delox joined those dinners, those
lo dijo eso Pues delox unió a esas cenas
little dinners, no, I
a las cenitas esas no yo yo creo
genuinely believe that his life revolves
genuinamente que su vida se gira en
around that, I think he turns off the
torno a eso yo creo que apaga la compo
computer and they talk to someone.  day by
el coso y hablan con alguien el día a
day they go to buy bread and they tell the lady at
día van a comprar el pan y le dicen a la
the bakery you know what's left is
de la panadería vos sabes que te queda
the dog going away
el se va el
right I mean in this he's
perro verdad O sea en esto tiene razón
totally right we've seen here al
totalmente el hemos visto aquí al al
gubel a little based and says javel
gubel un poco basado y dice javel
wigs gibel puts me in the in the
pelucas gibel me pone en la en la
discussion
tertulia
the most intuitive and intelligent discussion member
el tertuliano más intuitivo e
far above don't
inteligente muy por encima de no nos
insult us or we'll file a lawsuit
insultes o te ponemos una demanda
pioneer nerd face such an insult
pionera cara de empollón tal insulto
Defines my day to day perfection in
Define mi día a día la perfección de
fact it's the reason why in three
hecho es el motivo por el que en tres
days I only made five posts I'll
días Solo hice cinco publicaciones Ya
only talk about ages in my personal life
solo habro de edas en mi vida personal
well son that comment hurt you you
bueno hijo que te ha dolido ese
look angry in a
comentario poí Se te ve ardido en un
tweet because it bothers you let's see we have to
tweet poí que te molesta a ver hay que
talk a little with head How strange it is I do
hablar un poco con cabeci Qué raro es
n't come out
salgo no
very what is this [ __ ] that you've put me
muy qué es esto cabrón que me has puesto
here place eh important for your
aquí lugar eh importante para tu
story because when you became
historia porque cuando te distes a
known to the fullest with Win michu and also at
conocer a tope con Win michu y además en
that time many people told you how
aquella época mucha gente te decía como
you are Win michu's friend [ __ ] I have
eres el amigo de Win michu [__] Tengo
pending This video of Joaquín Yes let's go
pendiente Este vídeo de Joaquín Sí vamos
not of Joaquín is  from a person who
no de Joaquín es de una persona que lo
has interviewed him yes it's true I get a
ha entrevistado sí es verdad me sale
lot in recommended This video
mucho en recomendado Este vídeo la
Win michu's pet all that how do you
mascota de Win michu todo eso cómo
remember that stage dude I have it all
recuerdas esa etapa tío lo tengo todo
together about the shows the trip to Japan
junto lo de los shows el viaje a Japón
all that a doesn't want to know about and six
todo esa a no quiere sabera de y seis
here something out of cordiality you
aquí algo por cordialidad época de you
Planet era I have everything very together s it's
Planet lo tengo todo muy junto s que es
true that now I don't have the same
verdad que ahora no tengo la misma
relationship with him that I had of
relación con con él que que tenía de de
planning to be together every [ __ ] day
plan de de estar juntos cada [__] día
but we get along not in the way that
pero nos llevamos bien no en plan de que
we talk every day but I don't know we
nos hablemos cada día pero yo que sé nos
answer each other stories I like to know
contestamos storis a mí me gusta saber
that he's been doing well doing his thing and
que él estado bien haciendo su movida y
he likes to know that I'm doing well
a él le gusta saber que estoy bien
doing mine all paths
haciendo la mía todos los caminos se
separate and come together at some point and
separan y se juntan en algún momento y
if they get back together I mean I don't know I don't
si se vuelven a juntar o sea no sé yo no
have any bad memories deide Uf baby
tengo ningún mal recuerdo deide Uf baby
doll red and the red panties
doll rojo y las truzas rojas abuelo
horny grandpa I asked you for a greeting for
cachondo te pedí una felicitación para
Lina not that you became the gift I
Lina no que te convirtieras en el regalo
already congratulated her I already congratulated her but I have
ya la felicité ya la felicité pero la he
congratulated her not because you tell me you
felicitado no porque me lo digas tú
look cute I don't give a damn  you
pintam mona a mí me la suda que me lo
tell me I congratulated her because I
digas tú la he felicitado porque la he
saw the beautiful Lina By the way,
visto al al bellezón de Lina Por cierto
from here I send her another kiss okay And I
de Aquí le mando otro beso vale Y he
saw that it was her birthday on Twitter and I
visto que era su cumpleaños en Twitter y
congratulated her of course not How would I
la he felicitado por supuesto no Como
do with you if I see that it's your [ __ ]
haría contigo si veo que es tu [__]
birthday if I see that it's your [ __ ]
cumpleaños si veo que es tu [__]
birthday I will block you probably because you
cumpleaños te bloqueo seguramente porque
disgust me of him or of that time and you have had
me das asco de él ni de de esa época y
similar trajectories
habéis tenido trayectoria similares
because you both get off the wave I think it's
porque los dos os bajáis de la ola creo
also important to say enough to
que es importante también decir basta
change stages no and say Well I've already
cambiar de etapa no y decir Bueno ya me
passed YouTube like this Now I
he pasado YouTube de esta forma Ahora
want to do something else that fulfills me more
quiero hacer otra cosa que me llene más
or but it's complicated eh man when something
o pero es complicado eh tío cuando algo
is giving you so much peace there and bro and a
te está dando tanta paz ahí y bro y
lot of people consider you successful which was what
mucha gente os considera exitoso que era
you said was what
lo que tú decías era lo que más te
caught your attention the most that you
llamaba la atención de que tú muchas
often said [ __ ] people think
veces decías [__] la gente se piensa
that I'm famous how about I have a
que soy famoso que tal que tengo una
[ __ ] life and I'm broken
vida de la [__] y yo estoy roto por
inside really Well also the thing is that
dentro realmente Bueno también es que el
success is different for each person
éxito cada para cada persona es
dude for me right now at
diferente tío para mí ahora mismo en
this point in life
este punto en el que estoy en la vida el
success is knowing that I'm doing what I
éxito es saber que estoy haciendo lo que
want to do like it  wanna do I'm
quiero hacer como lo quiero hacer estoy
having fun like a kid and doing whatever the
gozándome como un niño y haciendo lo que
hell I want man well guys let's
me sale de los huevos tío pues chicos
go Sure but he's
nos vamos Claro pero es que ha tenido la
lucky enough to be editing paon Play I
suerte de que está editando paon Play me
imagine he has a
imagino que le tendrá un sueldo de la
[ __ ] salary Joaquin Maybe Cobra
[__] [__] Joaquín A lo mejor Cobra
will do the same as me eh being
hará lo mismo que yo eh estando
completely retired back to your house let
completamente retirado vuelta a tu casa
's go to the house to the cave to the house to
vamos a la casa a la cueva a la casa a
the mansion to the house let's see well I have
la mansión para casa a ver pues yo tengo
my issues and internal [ __ ] but it's not
mi movidas y [__] interna pero no es
something I can compare with anyone honestly
algo que compara con nadie sinceramente
I wouldn't like to see myself telling my
no me gustaría verme contándole mi
problem to someone I'm so used to
problema a alguien me acostumbrado tanto
being so unwell in quotes that I don't care anymore
a estar mal entre comillas que ya me da
being well I'm totally
igual estar bien te lo digo totalmente
serious mind you mind mind you eh What a nice
en serio ojo eh ojo eh Qué bonita
surprise What a nice surprise the places
sorpresa Qué bonita sorpresa el lugares
always surprise us and suddenly we
siempre nos sorprende y de repente
were talking about that e that Win
estábamos hablando de que e de que Win
michu wants to sue Pablo Franco or
michu quiere demandar a Pablo franco o
at least that's what dal veira says is that
por lo menos eso dice dal veira es que
D veira's information is not usually
la información de D veira no suele ser
very very reliable I'm afraid to get on
muy muy fiable me da miedo meterme en
Twitter Eh I'm afraid to get on
Twitter Eh me da miedo meterme en
Twitter because suddenly there are a lot of
Twitter porque de repente hay mucha
chetas lately be This is what
chetas últimamente sea Esto es lo que
Pablo put it's not worth it  you've never been
puso Pablo no vale que nunca estuviste
to char roulette you've never hit a
en char rulet que no has pegado un
bottle in your life and besides his
botellazo en tu vida y que además se
name is Marlo come on yeah it's like he
llama marlo venga que sí es como que lo
wants to negga everything and that's it no that
quiere negga todo y ya está no que
besides his name is Marlo come on yeah here I'm
además se llama marlo venga que sí aquí
waiting for the lawsuit things are going to go
espero la demanda que me van a venir
well for me but I think Win
bien las cosas pero yo creo que Win
michu hasn't Let's see it's that of course like
michu no ha A ver es que claro como
nauter also said that wh wh What are you
también nauter dijo lo de que qu qu Qué
doing dude Why do you think you're funny dude I
haces tío Por qué te crees gracioso tío
mean why do you think Why do you think you're
o sea por qué te crees Por qué te crees
funny do you think that anyone here in
gracioso crees que alguien de aquí de la
our community considers you funny
comunidad nuestra te considera gracioso
defend yourself claim do you think that anyone in our
defiéndete alega crees que alguien de la
community considers you funny
comunidad te considera gracioso
effective Wonder no you're not funny
effective Wonder no no eres gracioso
you're an idiot eh And what I said I mean of
eres [__] eh Y lo dicho o sea yo
course the thing is that nauter
claro es que la movida es que que nauter
said like Win michu had said that he was
dijo como que Win michu había dicho que
going to sue well Win michu himself
iba a demandar bueno Win michu mismo lo
put it on his I don't remember if it was a tweet
puso en su no me acuerdo si fue un tweet
or an Instagram yes I have sued
o un Instagram sí tengo demandado a
five or six youtubers and it was never known
cinco o seis youtubers y nunca se supo
who they were then nauter said that in the
Quiénes eran luego nauter dijo que en el
trial he said No no to Javi to Ada everything to
juicio dijo No no al Javi al Ada todo a
us  Nothing has arrived, the
nosotros no nos ha llegado nada la
truth is, and I think we have received
verdad y creo que nos han lleg llegado
lawsuits after that. But well, that's why I do
demandas después que esa Pero bueno por
n't think so. Okay, I don't want you to put it on me,
eso no creo esp tú no quiero que me la
don't put it on me, okay, but that's why I do
pongas no me la pongas vale pero que que
n't think anyone will sue anymore.
por eso no creo que demande más nadie
Joaquín talked about what Win Mocho did
Joaquín habló de lo que hacía Win mocho
and he distanced himself from him well. Yes, I think
y se desligó de él bien Sí yo creo que a
Joaquín, I think he didn't like
Joaquín yo creo que no le gustaban
some things, now I see why the closet
algunas cosas ya veo por qué el armario
was open XD. It's true that you've got me up to
estaba abierto XD verdad me tenéis hasta
my neck
la punta de la [__]
[Music]
[Música]